Silas Morales

Front-End Dev

818-633-8742 silas.mora22@gmail.com linkedin.com/example githut.com/example Sherman Oaks, CA 91401

Summary

Solution-driven web developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.

Educational Background

True Coders | Full Stack Web Development

Dec 2022 - present

Associates of Arts(A.A)

L.A.V.C May 2012

Tech Skills

Computer Languages

- HMTL5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- React
- SQL
- Node
- Express

Projects

- WeatherApp
- Amazon Clone
- Pokedex
- Ambulance Booking System

Relevant Experience

Leadership | Team Lead

Blend Labs

June. 2021 - Nov 2022

Insurance Sales | Advisor

Blend Labs

Aug 2019 - June 2021